UNITE Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/024 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Chinatown Manpower Project, Inc. Workplace Literacy Program, 1 (Box 139)
- Chinatown Manpower Project, Inc. Workplace Literacy Program, 1 (Box 140)
- UNITE, 1 (Box 141)
- 10/26/1988; 3/18/1986, 1 (Box 142)
- Exec. Bd. Meeting - 8/21/1984, 1 (Box 143)
- 9/27/1988, 1 (Box 144)
- Shop Rep, 1 (Box 145)
- 4/25/1989, 1 (Box 146)
- KQ and Alice T. - re: Holiday pay rules, 1 (Box 147)
- Sue and Emily; Betty and Mary; Katey and Mr. Ka; katey and Raymond, 1 (Box 148)
- Edgar Rommy - 12/19/1988, 1 (Box 149)
- April Union Voice 1988, 1 (Box 150)
- 6/9 and 6/16 (no other labeling), 1 (Box 151)
- Sam and Betty - re: Holiday Fun 2/1984; re: Grievance handling, 1 (Box 152)
- 2/1988 - Chinatown Radio Shows, 1 (Box 153)
- Black History - CWCB, 1 (Box 154)
- 3/26/1983, 1 (Box 155)
- Union Voice - Q and A with Howie Zinn - 2/1988, 1 (Box 156)
- Opening Session - negotiation, 1 (Box 157)
- Sept. Union Voice - 9/12/1985, 1 (Box 158)
- Union Voice for Nov. 1985, 1 (Box 159)
- YWCA Local 23-25 Day Camp 7/17/1983, 1 (Box 160)
- Union Voice - Local 23-25, ILGWU - 6/23/1984 and 6/30/1984, 1 (Box 161)
- 7/5 Show - Topic: Hong Kong, 1 (Box 162)
- 9/1/1987 - Union Voice - Betty and Randy Live, 1 (Box 163)
- Chinatown Manpower Projects, Inc. Workplace Literacy Program, 1 (Box 164)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 201)
- JB Exec Bd - 5/4/2005, 1 (Box 202)
- SAUP Rep - 10/30/1984, 1 (Box 203)
- Press Conference, 1 (Box 204)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 205)
- 9/15/2004 Meeting, 1 (Box 206)
- 6/19, 1 (Box 207)
  only labeling on tape
- Tony - 1/24/1984, 1 (Box 208)
- 8/21/1984, 1 (Box 209)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 210)
- 9/26/1985, 1 (Box 211)
- Triangle Fire - 9/30/1991, 1 (Box 212)
- 1/24/1984, 1 (Box 213)
- Ex.Bd. - 1/27/1988, 1 (Box 214)
- Radio Program on Workers proposes for a new C.B.A., 1 (Box 215)
- 1997 Exec. Board Meeting, 1 (Box 216)
- U.A.F.T. - 1/23/1986, 1 (Box 217)
- Executive Board Meeting - 3/26, 1 (Box 218)
- H and W - 1/23/1985, 1 (Box 219)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 220)
- 4/25/1984, 1 (Box 221)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 222)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 223)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 224)
- Exec. Bd. Meeting - 1/27/1988, 1 (Box 225)
- 6/26/1986, 1 (Box 226)
- Press Conference - 5/27/1985, 1 (Box 227)
- G.M.M. -- 3/27/1985, 1 (Box 228)